Guide to the School of Hotel Administration. Master of Management in Hospitality Program records, 1996-2009.
School of Hotel Administration. Master of Management in Hospitality Program records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
School of Hotel Administration. Master of Management in Hospitality Program records, 1996-2009.
28-4-4073
Cornell University. School of Hotel Administration. Master of Management in Hospitality Program.
3.4 cubic feet.
Printed material
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes course learning outcome documents for various courses.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes course learning outcome documents for various courses.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.
Subjects:
Hotel management schools -- New York (State) -- Ithaca.; Hotel management -- Study and teaching.
Form and Genre Terms:
Videotapes.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Course: Corporate Finance - Linda Canina, Instructor, Fall 2008/Spring 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Course: Graduate Marketing Management - Chekitan Dev, Instructor, Fall 2008/Spring 2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Course: Professional Development I and II - Lisa Shaffer and Molly deRoos, Instructors, Fall 2008/Spring 2009 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Courses: Human Behavior in Organizations and Leadership Development Program - Tim Hinkin, Instructor, Fall 2008/Spring 2009 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Course: Managerial Accounting - James Hesford, Instructor, Fall 2008/Spring 2009 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Course: Operations Management - Sherri Kimes, Instructor, Fall 2008/Spring 2009 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Course: MMH Discussion Forums in Hospitality Management - Dean Michael Johnson, Instructor, Fall 2008/Spring 2009 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Course: Master Class, Las Vegas - Richard Penner, Instructor, Fall 2008/Spring 2009 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Course: Managerial Communications - David Lennox, Instructor, Fall 2008/Spring 2009 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Course: Human Resources Management - Michael Sturman, Instructor, Fall 2008/Spring 2009 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Course: Properties Development and Planning - Richard Penner, Instructor, Fall 2008/Spring 2009 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Course: Hospitality Strategy - Cathy Enz, Instructor, Fall 2008/Spring 2009 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Course: Managerial Accounting - Chung Lai Hong, Instructor, Fall 2008/Spring 2009 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Course: CNI - Managerial Communication - Joo-Seng Tan, Instructor, Fall 2008/Spring 2009 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Course: CNI - Managerial Accounting - Chung Lai Hong and Chan Ying Lock, Instructors, Fall 2008/Spring 2009 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Course: CNI - Competitive Strategies for Hospitality Industry - Shobha Das, Instructor, Fall 2008/Spring 2009 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Course: CNI - Human Resource Management - Wee Beng Geok, Instructor, Fall 2008/Spring 2009 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Course: Information Systems Management - Erica Wagner, Instructor, Fall 2008/Spring 2009 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Course: CNI - Managerial Communication - Michael Baker, Instructor, Fall 2009/Spring 2010 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Course: Corporate Finance - Linda Canina, Instructor, Fall 2009/Spring 2010 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Course: CNI - Human Resource Management, Fall 2009/Spring 2010 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Course: Human Resources Management - Gabe Piccoli, Instructor, Fall 2007/Spring 2008 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Course: Professional Development 1 and 2 Career Management - Lisa Shaffer and Molly deRoos, Instructors, Fall 2007/Spring 2008 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Course: Strategic Management - Arturs Kalnins, Instructor, Fall 2007/Spring 2008 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Course: Human Behavior in Organizations - Tim Hinkin, Instructor, Fall 2007/Spring 2008 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Course: Properties Development and Planning - Richard Penner, Instructor, Fall 2007/Spring 2008 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Course: Management Communications - Amy Newman, Instructor, Fall 2007/Spring 2008 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Course: Deliverable for January Externship- Jan deRoos, Instructor, Fall 2007/Spring 2008 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Course: Graduate Marketing Management - Chekitan Dev, Instructor, Summer 2007 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Course: MMH Charrette - Richard Penner, Instructor, Fall 2007/Spring 2008 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Course: Information Systems Management - Gabe Piccoli, Instructor, Fall 2007/Spring 2008 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Course: Managerial Accounting - James Hesford, Instructor, Summer 2007 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Course: MMH Discussion Forums in Hospitality Management - Dean Michael Johnson, Instructor, Fall 2007/Spring 2008 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Course: Corporate Finance - Linda Canina, Instructor, Summer 2007 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Videos and Reports of Team Presentations, 1996-2000; V-6841-6857 (Box 3)
- Videos and Reports of Team Presentations, 2000-2001; V-6858-6875 (Box 4)